Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors, but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is Gimme S'mores. Let me show you
how to make it. For those of you
unfamiliar with this flavor, it is a
toasted marshmallow base. So, we are
using what is essentially my normal
vanilla base, but we are grabbing about
a half serving of mini marshmallows and
toasting them up because that's what it
takes to get the real authentic flavor.
So, after your base is all mixed, you
can just throw those in on top and then
throw it in the freezer for at least 16
hours. Take it out, run it under hot
water for about a minute, and then throw
it in the creamy on the light ice cream
setting. The creamy will basically mix
those marshmallows in for you, so don't
worry about them getting stuck in the
blade. Now on to the mix-ins. This
flavor has a chocolate cookie swirl,
fudge flakes, and a graham cracker
swirl. So to recreate all of that, we're
using two Oreo thins, cream removed just
to reduce the calories a little bit. And
then we're using my chocolate chip hack.
I've made a bunch of videos about this.
Basically just melt down some chocolate
chips with some coconut oil and then use
that as a mixin. I find that these
homemade chocolate chips are way, way
better than normal chocolate chips as a
mixin. And then all you have to do is
top it with a little bit of crushed
graham cracker. And then optionally a
few little mini marshmallows.